ton of people get this problem wrong it
says what is the value of 5x and we have
a diagram we have a 90 degree angle
right here which means that this angle
right here is also going to be 90
degrees because this is a straight line
and since this angle right here is 90
degrees that means that if we were to
add up all of these inside angles x plus
2x plus 2x all of them have to add up to
90 degrees so let's go ahead and do that
down here so we have an x
we have a 2x and we have a 2x and all of
these angles added up has to equal 90
degrees okay so now we can just add up
like terms x 2x and 2x that's going to
be equal to 5x and we have an equals 90.
and just like that we don't have to do
any more work because our answer is